

18/06/1995



tungduongnguyen1806@gmail.com



0967604571



aboutduong.wordpress.com



behance.net/tnqdnq2



63 Thai Thinh st., Dong Da dist., Hanoi

SKILL

CONTENT/COPY-WRITING

PUBLIC RELATIONS

CREATIVE

PLANNING

DESIGN

VIDEO EDIT



SOFTWARE

















LANGUAGE

IELTS
OVERALL 6.5

Listening 6.0

Writing 7.0

Reading 7.0

Speaking 6.5

DUONG NGUYEN

PR - MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Hello! My name is Tung Duong. I am an enthusiastic person about marketing, language, and art. I have more than 3 years working in Marketing field, both in Vietnam clients and foreign corporations. I always work with responsibility and a creative mind. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines. My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

English Now Global (Education)

CONTENT MARKETING EXECUTIVE

12/2019 - NOW

Build content marketing strategies and write content on mass media (both offline & online channels)

Develop Digital content marketing campaigns (Facebook Ads, Email Marketing, Zalo)

Create Branding & Marketing campaign (contest, cross-selling, event, etc)

Lead Video project and write video script

Manage Internal communication & Marketing Admin works

Emeralda Management Group (Hospitality Industry) 03/2018 - 07/2019
PR - MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Manage Sponsorship & Cooperation activities

Maintain and develop Press Relations and collaborate with Agency
Buid PR and content marketing strategies and write on mass media

Work with KOLs, Suppliers & Production teams

Support sales volume and other marketing events

iCheck Corp (E-commerce and Technology)
CONTENT MARKETING EXECUTIVE

09/2017 - 03/2018

Build video and social content marketing strategies Create advertising content as a publisher platform Write for search engine optimization (SEO) Manage Content & Design outsourcing team

Freelancer Experience 2015 - 2020

as Entertaining Content Creator at Eyeplus Media, Script Writer at VLIVE.TV (Korea),

Video Marketing Producer at Smile Up Dental, Content Writing at Happynest,

Marketing Executive at The Global Citizen Group (Singapore)

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATE

The Academy of Journalism and Communication

2013 - 2017

FACULTY OF PUBLIC RELATIONS AND ADVERTISING - ADVERTISING BACHELOR

KF Global e-School (Korea)

2015

NEW MEDIA ADVERTISING IN KOREA

Arena Multimedia

2014

DESIGN PRO CERTIFICATE & SCHOLARSHIP